<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<legalnotice id="legalnotice">
         <para>Χορηγείται άδεια αντιγραφής, διανομής και/ή τροποποίησης του παρόντος εγγράφου υπό τους όρους της ελεύθερης άδειας τεκμηρίωσης GNU (GFDL), έκδοσης 1.1 ή οποιασδήποτε μεταγενέστερης έκδοσής της από το ίδρυμα ελεύθερου λογισμικού, χωρίς αμετάβλητα τμήματα, κείμενα εξωφύλλου και κείμενα οπισθόφυλλου. Μπορείτε να βρείτε αντίγραφο της GFDL σε αυτό <ulink type="help" url="ghelp:fdl">σύνδεσμος</ulink> ή στο αρχείο COPYING-DOCS που διανέμεται με αυτό το εγχειρίδιο.</para>
          <para>Αυτό το εγχειρίδιο είναι μέρος μιας συλλογής εγχειριδίων GNOME που διανέμονται με την GFDL. Εάν θέλετε να διανείμετε αυτό το εγχειρίδιο ξεχωριστά από τη συλλογή, μπορείτε να το κάνετε προσθέτοντας ένα αντίγραφο της άδειας στο εγχειρίδιο, όπως περιγράφεται στην ενότητα 6 της άδειας.</para>
 
         <para>Πολλά από τα ονόματα χρησιμοποιούνται από εταιρείες για διάκριση των προϊόντων τους και υπηρεσιών δηλώνονται ως εμπορικά σήματα. Όπου αυτά τα ονόματα εμφανίζονται σε οποιοδήποτε τεκμηρίωση GNOME και τα μέλη του σχεδίου τεκμηρίωσης GNOME γνωρίζουν αυτά τα εμπορικά σήματα, τα ονόματα είναι με κεφαλαία γράμματα ή αρχικά κεφαλαία γράμματα.</para>
 
         <para>DOCUMENT AND MODIFIED VERSIONS OF THE DOCUMENT ARE PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THE GNU FREE DOCUMENTATION LICENSE WITH THE FURTHER UNDERSTANDING THAT: <orderedlist>
                 <listitem>
                   <para>DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES THAT THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT IS FREE OF DEFECTS MERCHANTABLE, FIT FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGING. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE QUALITY, ACCURACY, AND PERFORMANCE OF THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT IS WITH YOU. SHOULD ANY DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION PROVE DEFECTIVE IN ANY RESPECT, YOU (NOT THE INITIAL WRITER, AUTHOR OR ANY CONTRIBUTOR) ASSUME THE COST OF ANY NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. THIS DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY CONSTITUTES AN ESSENTIAL PART OF THIS LICENSE. NO USE OF ANY DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT IS AUTHORIZED HEREUNDER EXCEPT UNDER THIS DISCLAIMER· AND UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES AND UNDER NO LEGAL THEORY, WHETHER IN TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE, SHALL THE AUTHOR, INITIAL WRITER, ANY CONTRIBUTOR, OR ANY DISTRIBUTOR OF THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT, OR ANY SUPPLIER OF ANY OF SUCH PARTIES, BE LIABLE TO ANY PERSON FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY CHARACTER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF GOODWILL, WORK STOPPAGE, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, OR ANY AND ALL OTHER DAMAGES OR LOSSES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO USE OF THE DOCUMENT AND MODIFIED VERSIONS OF THE DOCUMENT, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY SHALL HAVE BEEN INFORMED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.</para>
                 </listitem>
           </orderedlist></para>
   </legalnotice>
